

julien@cappiello.fr | 044 55 48 84 33 49 José Linares 1636, Col. Del Valle, D.F 35 Years old Single French Living in México



LSEN OR

EXPERIENCE

2+ Aplications Android sur Google Play:

• SP Mobile, Pemex Checker...

SP Marketing, Mex. 2014 - 2015

Development Team Leader

- Dev. Android / PHP SP Mobile
- · Supervision for Wordpress sites, PHP apps

Pedregal University, Mex. 2012 - 2014

Teacher

- · Algorithmic in C
- Android programation Introduction

Café Amate, Mex. 2012 - 2013

Owner - Coffee shop, Internet café, IT Consulting

• Project / Team Management

Bancomer (Teknei), Mex. 2011 - 2012

Team Leader in Autoservice project

- Managed a 4 people team
- Managed ATM, Java, JAM

Sodexho Pass (Zappa), Mex. 2008 - 2009

Java, J2EE, Struts - SEV application

- Project: Electronic Voucher System
- · Oracle, OAS, Oracle Forms, Oracle Reports

Air France (Eurogiciel), Fr. 2007 - 2008

Java, J2EE

- Development, maintenance of applications
- · Webspere, Struts, Oracle, WSAD

RNT de México, Monterrey. 2004 - 2006

Java, J2EE, Mobiles Technologies

 Developed a Content Management Platform for Cell Phones - WAP

Web Developer 2001 - Présent

Freelance

- · Portafolio: http://julien.cappiello.fr
- · Wordpress, Joomla

PROFIL

Senior Software Engineer with International and interdisciplinary experience desiring to work with latest IT technologies in culture or ecology. Adaptable, bilingue, creative and punctual. Project management in teams. I Need to be proud of my job.

SKILLS

Developpment	Web Design
Java / J2E / Android	Wordpress, Joomla
Spring, Struts	HTML 5, CSS 3
PHP, SQL, JS	Adobe Dw, Ph, Id
XML, JSON	JQuery[UI][Mobile]
Webservices REST, SOAP	
Eclipse, Netbeans, IntelliJ	
WebSphere, Tomcat, Apache	

EDUCATION

High School of engineering

Git, Clearcase, SVN, Redmine

ESIEA, 1998-2004 Paris, France

Master Degree: Eco-Anthropology

National Museum of Natural History 2010 Paris, France

LANGUAGES

- French: (mother tongue)
- Spanish: Bilingue (10 years in México)
- English: fluent(825 pt-TOEIC en 2003)
- Portuguese: Basic Level

ACTIVITIES

- Kendo (2th Dan)
- Music, Son Jarocho
- Travelling, Photography